hey everybody checking 101 here okay so
over the past couple of days I've been
mentioning on my live streams and on my
vlog channel and on my main channel that
I'm going to be doing this I was going
to do a video discussing crossover
battles and mainly uh this was confirmed
to me yesterday when I uploaded a video
of a very seemingly innocent v-log on my
channel where me and my friend Phil just
went along shopping you know just like
okay this is you know I I haven't shown
a lot of other people in my v-log so you
know there you go I'll just post this
very innocent just thing maybe I'll get
a few yucks out of it yeah and then I
discovered I knew this already I really
did but just to confirm the fact that
even if it's a video that doesn't have
anything to do with anime if you so much
as even mention a crossover battle and
who you think would win or lose who
would win ichigo or naruto this is a
main issue right now that might be
making a series about this naruto
comment section fucking extravaganza ha
ha never ceases to amaze me actually it
kind of does you guys really scare me
getsuga tensho is millions times
stronger than all Naruto's Rasengan
Barto Rasengan is two weeks so ross and
shuriken Rasengan and the rest of them
are pointless
also staged mode is crap in addition
ichigo has blue vein do you know what
that even is that is crazy defense
ichigo with the raw power beats Naruto
just like he beat Aizen normal bankai
ichigo vs all power off a Naruto Ichigo
is dead not okay uh well as you can see
the resounding opinion is that Ichigo
would steamroll Naruto in an instant and
the problem here is in the video and my
personal opinion on the matter is that
Naruto would in fact win so and there's
also a comment to is on a previous video
and I misplaced it somewhere but it
essentially came up with two points and
that's what kind of got me on this
warpath hole to begin with that Naruto
cannot is not a spiritually aware being
and therefore would not be able to see
Ichigo and along with this Ichigo is
able to fly so you know I've tried maybe
this
this vlog and I just thought you know
what I'm just gonna put a vlog out there
people may be seein to see this little
bit of my own life and instead the
comments section is magnetized toward
this I'm tired I'm done I'm doing this
video now I was going to give a little
bit more time to see how maybe I could
pan out because the thing with crossover
battles is pretty much everybody in the
anime manga community has at least
mentioned it or has a separate series on
it or other videos on YouTube that you
can look into it and I thought well
there's no point me doing it because now
all this is going to result in is just
me saying who would win who would lose a
bunch of people in the comments some
agree with me most of them probably not
leaving an entire you know like a
hundred page freaking arguments with
somebody else on why Ichigo or Naruto
would win so it just seems more trouble
than it's worth but you know I start to
think that you know that's actually a
good thing that there's multiple
different opinions on YouTube because
that way if you don't like the way I'm
presenting it because I'm gonna do it my
own way I'm gonna have my own rules and
regulations I'm gonna have my own little
way I'm gonna do this if you don't agree
with me then go watch somebody else you
do agree with but that's a good thing
that there's different opinions because
a lot of this stuff is variable factors
stuff that is not concrete stuff that
has never been confirmed and never will
be confirmed no matter how much you
think Naruto would freaking own Ichigo
or Ichigo would stop Naruto's freaking
Fox form into the freakin dirt with
getsuga tensho
there is absolutely no final answer the
only conceivable way that would happen
is if t-take Kubo creator of bleach and
Masashi Kishimoto creator of Naruto
got together mostly up there not own
free will and by droves of fans forcing
them into a room together to write a
definitive manga chapter where Ichigo
and Naruto fight to the death that's the
only way that's going to go down and I
don't think that's ever going to go down
because no Noman gonca wants that no
Mongkok i wants to get it together with
another one be like hey you want to make
a series where my character gets the
shit kicked out of him by yours you know
so your mongo getting way more views and
mine will get ridiculed for all eternity
I mean look at the look at the one piece
and Torico crossovers yeah we saw fights
between one piece and Torico and even
the goq in the Dragon Ball Z crossover
with Goku but it wasn't like a serious
fight I mean it's not going to come out
with
be dead on the ground and Goku Super
Saiyan 3 triumphant covered in his blood
you know it's going to be equal so
that's the problem when you have
official crossovers and you know like I
said the problems with fandom crossovers
are the variable factors so there we go
I'm going to do this I wrote down my
little cheat sheet of all the abilities
and everything I thought that each of
them have to attack defense speed
augmentation abilities and other
miscellaneous abilities so that's five
crucial groups we're talking about here
now once again I'm gonna do this my own
way you're probably going to UM up it
for opinions I'm open for people saying
oh maybe you should do this instead of
this but I know I'm going to get
comments they're saying like oh well you
did this instead of this so therefore
your entire fight is not even viable
because the way you did it this is the
way I see the fairness okay first thing
we do before we even discuss actual
Ichigo Naruto in terms of fighting
ability and characters is the area in
which they're fighting and other stuff
we have to sort out by the way because
these two characters are from different
universes they had draw their power from
different sources ichigo uses reaction
rate reishi Naruto uses chakra and the
nine tails Fox and everything so that's
where his powers were based on so we
cannot have them fight we can't just
have Ichigo popping in the Naruto's
world or vice-versa we have to make a
neutral universe that's where the
variables come into play here so neutral
universe they both just appear in the
universe okay in this universe let's
just say physics apply the same way
Naruto can still use chakra and gather
chakra ichigo still has this reishi and
can still use reishi based attacks
another major crucial issue here is that
Naruto is not as spiritually aware being
there for Ichigo with freaking own him
because Naruto will not be able to see
him it is true that Naruto has the
ability to sense emotions through his
nine tails chakra and that would make
sense that you would be able to sense
his emotion but at the same time not
being able to see him would be a crucial
disadvantage here's what I have to say
about that and this is probably where a
lot of people are going to get mad at me
you have to look at each of their
personalities Ichigo and Naruto are both
a very typical Shonen hero in the sense
that they like to have a fair fight they
don't like to fight anyone against the
odds or you know like anything that's a
majorly tip to their favor I mean
they'll take a chance --is of off
tunity in battle you know and eat when
like if eysan were to you know like you
know if Ichigo were to hit eyes and he
gets knocked into a building ichigo's
not going to be you know oh well I'm
gonna wait him to get back up well
sometimes he does that but I'm not going
to wait for him to get back up I'm gonna
charge right at him
but in terms of the actual basis of the
fight look when ichigo fought against
doki aura he went hollow form ripped off
ouki auras arm and leg after he regained
consciousness he offered Farooqi aura to
rip off his arm and leg so it would be a
fair fight so you really have to think
to yourself Ichigo just saw Naruto do
you really think Ichigo would be like
huh look at that blonde idiot he thinks
he's such a badass he can't even see me
I'm just gonna walk up to him and slit
his frickin throat with my sword Ichigo
would never do that
so in terms of a fight between Ichigo
and Naruto and not Naruto not being able
to see Ichigo that wouldn't even be a
fight and I don't mean that that would
not be a fight as Ichigo would
immediately 100% win I mean Ichigo would
not fight Naruto in those conditions
that just would not happen in this
neutral universe Naruto can see Ichigo
vice versa they could both see each
other's abilities now another major kind
of crucial thing we have to determine
here is the ability of reishi and chakra
because Naruto and Ichigo both have a
separate power sources and people are
going to wonder like okay well you know
does reiatsu you know can Ichigo since
Naruto because he doesn't have reiatsu
or is in chakra okay both of them at the
same time you gotta have to look at this
Naruto and Ichigo aren't really good at
sensing the respective energies Ichigo
is never very good at sensing reiatsu to
begin with
Naruto without without the nine tails or
sage mode chakras help was not able to
sense he's not a sensory-type ninja he's
not able to just being like he's not
caring or any money as I kind of like oh
there's no ninja over there he's never
been able to do that with sage mode his
senses are heightened to insane
superhuman degrees and he can certainly
hear things and see things he's never
been able to see before and through the
nine tails chakra he's able to sense
emotions but on his own
Naruto is not able to sense chakra so
that doesn't even apply anyway so the
whole sensing issue that that doesn't
even have to apply so I think that's
everything all the nitpicks we have to
get out of the way in terms of how the
fight would be set up so neutral
universe Naruto can see Ichigo
sensing is not really an issue
because of the they're both in ability
they really do it to begin with so now
let's get to the actual how the fight
would start off or play off now you know
I was going to think of how to do this
if Ichigo Naruto we're kind of kind of
start off in their own you know respect
like normal state Ichigo shikai and then
if the fight increases not Ichigo jumps
to bankai but really how many times have
we seen in the series even up to this
point we've seen in the series that
Ichigo just kind of goes ball and Kai
right away where he's been in bankai for
a period of time and you know even with
the war arc gnar has been pretty much
stuck in the ninetails clock cloaked
form for pretty much close to 100
chapters if that so I'm just going to
say off the bat
let's just say Naruto goes in the nine
tails cloak form because he's able to
control the to be basically him in
Kurama or on even footing right now so
he would be able to access the nine
tails chakra no problem Ichigo isn't
that depth at bankai so he would go
bankai directly as for the current
versions that were fighting or what
point in the time frame I'm going at I'm
going after them both as recent as
humanly possible so in terms of Naruto
he's able to use the nine tails chakra
he's able to transform into Quran on him
and Kurama can communicate back and
forth Sage Mode nights those cloak all
that stuff he's able to do Ichigo I had
to kind of twist around a little bit
because his powers are very sketchy
right now I know he's a Quincy and a lot
of people are thinking he's going to
whip out like a black Quincy Bo and you
know do all that crazy shit but we don't
know any of that yet um I had I know
he's getting a new sword soon from the
Maya but we had to go back because we
don't know what that new sword is going
to be or what it's going to look like or
how its powers are going to be different
from his current bankai so we're going
back with his original bankai after it
was restored by Rukia so the one that
hash fall broke essentially so we're
going with post time skip Ichigo before
his sword was broken and we're going
with current Naruto in terms of the
chapters alright so just to clarify that
ready to go with the actual comparison
between their attacks and defense speed
augments and other abilities I got my
bleach wristband there in my deidara
Akatsuki ring which is actually on the
right finger I believe I think it is I
hope okay so in terms of attacks let's
just go down the attack list here
ichigo's got gets a good 10 show he's
got enhanced strength through reiatsu
and his training he has bankai with an
enhanced black getsuga
he's got hollow masks I know we haven't
seen each ego uses hollow mass since the
time-skip
but it's such a massive chunk of his
powers and if I didn't mention it I'd be
under more scrutiny and plus we saw in
the last chapter with the Itachi that he
was selecting one that resembled very
closely to his hollow abilities so let's
just say hallo mask in the sense of the
hala mask he used against eyes and with
the the two lines there he also has a
focus get-together that he can channel
into his arm when he fought with Yura
and now the two abilities that
everyone's gonna well maybe ones not so
big one is the cero but he's only able
to use that info hollow form I'll get to
that when we get more into you know
later down the line in the fight I know
other visored such as Shinji and Masha
ro can just do a Sarah whenever they
want just with their masks ichigo's
never been displayed that ability he's
never shown trying to learn how to do a
cero so let's just say you can't use a
Sarah unless he's a full holo and the
other thing is his final gets to get ten
show and that's another thing that a lot
of people are saying right away that
ichigo's final getsugatensho would
immediately be able to split Naruto in
half and that's pretty much it right
there let's get that out of the way
right now okay number one we're not even
sure if he can do it again
so I mean you probably can but we're not
even sure if he can number two what he
really want to do it again and we have
to think about this Ichigo knew he could
not defeat Aizen he was pretty much
guaranteed he cannot defeat Aizen
although after he trained with ition in
the dong guy and he you know met tensa
zangetsu and everything it kind of was
apparent that he was able to basically
kick the shit out of Aizen without using
Vonnegut's content show but whatever
let's just say you know what do you
really want to waste all of his powers
on a one-shot and number number three he
doesn't like the Indian the exact
purpose of the power how it works it's
never been really shown exactly the
whole mechanics of this ability like we
know you know he turns into fool gets
ago mode raises his sword off uses mu
gets and then just darkness comes out of
nowhere and just splits everything right
down the middle I mean can it be dodged
can it be you know evaded or I'm sure it
can't be blocked just because of the raw
power but I mean if he misses with that
technique it's over I mean I mean it's
clear I mean
can you can't even say that it's
unavailable because we saw in that
chapter it just cuts everything right
down the middle so therefore by logic if
you were not in the direct path of the
attack if you were not in this point
that was split in half then you would be
technically evading the attack and
Ichigo would be out of power so I'm just
gonna say he wouldn't use the final
getsugatensho and then Robert Robert
Robert how dare you whatever okay let's
say so you know no final get to get in
show and Sarah only a full hallo okay so
those are basically all of ichigo's
offensive abilities now let's look how
they stack up to Naruto's Naruto has
shadow clones he has a Rasengan in
multiple forms he has massive Rasengan
Rasengan Rasen shuriken planetary
Rasengan twin rasen shuriken Sage Mode
Rasengan twin Rasengan normal it says so
he has multiple variations of the same
technique so we'll get back to that he
also has a sage mode and he also has
summoning abilities which he barely
rarely uses anymore and he also has
ninja tools he has you know we've seen
after the time-skip he just keeps
Scrolls on him so he's able to just you
know pop out a giant shuriken whenever
he wants to all right along with this
you know nara ichigo would of course
have a sort of obviously so here's what
we get into another major issue from the
comments that I've been reading anyway
pretty much everyone said well not
everybody but pretty much the main
consensus is you know ichigo's one get
touka tensho would be able to destroy
Naruto's Rasengan no matter what like
the power wouldn't even compare the way
I look at it is this way yes if Ichigo
was using a gessica tensho and Naruto
just had a regular-sized Rasengan then
yeah that would of course trump power
again in sense of not just for the fact
that naruto de can't throw a regular
Rasengan and you know easily just you
know that would rebound it but we also
have russ and shuriken plus the giant
orbital get fucked from 20 different
directions and call me suzy orbital
Rasengan barrage attack now that versus
against a Content show you can't really
say that this and this is so much
differential in power like there's like
oh yeah against those two things that'd
be such a major difference too and you
also can't really say like prep time for
the attack to create ichigo can just
swing his sword and use gets ago nor
takes time to create
yeah that used to be the case but
remember a lot has changed ever since he
accessed the ninetails fog Fox's chakra
he could probably produce this many Ross
Jenkins and I say probably because once
again can conjecture but he could
probably create this many Ross Jenkins
and shadow clones with little issue now
that he's has chrome on his side now um
going up against any kind of ninja tool
weapon that Naruto would use of course I
know he doesn't use them that much
anymore you never really use that much
to begin with but let's just say he
would use it in that situation Ichigo
would pretty much be able to destroy
anything that r2 pulls out even if it's
the most highly crafted metal technique
now Ichigo with zangetsu would be able
to crack anything I mean that's probably
never going to come up but I just had to
mention it just for the sake of
mentioning it also in terms of often
civilities you gotta look at the shadow
clones naruto is not very gifted at
using the substitution technique and if
you could use the substitution technique
i'd probably just call this fight just
now because ichigo doesn't have all
these different tactics he's pretty much
just a frontline fighter but Naruto is
able to create clones
he's been shown to be adept at switching
out with clones or you know deceiving
the enemy
I'm not saying Ichigo is like a major
idiot but in terms of battle strategy
and extreme tactics he's not really the
one you want to go to that would be
something more suited for a cooky
talking people that have been
battle-hardened warriors for hundreds of
years and know about battle tactics and
everything and you know and abilities at
the same time Naruto is not extremely
gifted at battle strategies either but
Naruto kind of went to school for this
that's kind of what the Ninja Academy
was for for learning about battle
tactics attacking from the shadows and
everything he wasn't the greatest
student I'm just saying Ichigo had a
regular education like me based around
you know just like regular studies and
everything Naruto's studies were based
around learning other stuff and plus
they live in a different world so even
if Naruto didn't know about this stuff
in school he would find him out about it
just in the way they fight because the
way characters fight in Naruto in the
way they fight in Bleach are two
completely different methods of
attacking also that we've seen that
Ichigo is not able to rapidly fire off
get touka ten shows yes we've seen that
he's able to you know fire it gets a go
and then another gets ago what I'm
saying is he's not able to do like you
know get sick attend show barrage or
something we've never seen like you know
a Gatling gun version gets a gat n show
okay so in a sense if Naruto use shadow
clones and I was like fifty freaking
Naruto's all with nine tails chakra
running around in free
SuperSpeed and we'll get to speed
running around in super fast and Ichigo
fires up against the contention getting
disorienting not knowing which one is
the real Naruto Naruto would have the
advantage there because he would have
multiple opportunities to chuck a
freaking Ross and jerk in an Ichigo and
we'll get into defensive later on but
let me just say right now if each ego
gets hit with one of those freaking
things oscillating and God knows how
many freaking frequencies that that
pretty much tears yourselves apart then
yeah I'm thinking that would sting a bit
I'm just going to say in terms of attack
and that could cause the most damage
over the you know quickest amount of
time I'm gonna give that one to Naruto
next up we have defensive abilities and
both in Naruto in each ego these are
very slim but basically for Ichigo we
have his reishi cushion we've seen that
before Ichigo is pretty good at
absorbing his reishi together is kind of
like a cushion so then when you get a
hit when he gets hit by an attack it
reduces the damage it doesn't always
reduce it completely but it takes less
he takes less damage than you normally
would have next up we also have holo
mass when he goes to the hala mask he's
able to take a lot more beating than he
normally is this was seen when he was
fighting against to cure each of you
oaky aura under normal circumstances
asaro was able to basically knock Ichigo
out with his hollow mask ability after
he you know regained it a little bit he
was able to basically resist you if you
are Sarah OH to get all together finally
we have probably the one that a lot of
people are mentioning the most that
Ichigo would have is blue vein blue vein
is the newest ability that Ichigo has
gained and it's basically a defensive
ability that was developed by the
Quincy's essentially you harden the
reishi inside of your blood vessels or
you modify to a sense where it's able to
basically resist attacks when juhabach
was about to stab ichigo point-blank in
the neck with a sword he was able to
block it subconsciously using blue thing
ichigo did not know he had the ability
it was more just like a reflexes thing
that he just gained after fighting after
our getting released from quill Gees
cage a lot of people are saying that
with blue vein active and you know
doesn't matter if in order to uses Ross
and shuriken or whatever ichigo's able
to resist that here's the problem I have
with that number one ichigo just gained
this ability therefore he didn't know he
was using it it was purely reflexive and
bland juhabach
even said
okay well I'll stab you again even
harder and even blue vein won't be able
to stop it so there is a clear limit to
ichigo's blue vein it's not as polished
as other bonded right members Chu of Ock
you know he was fairly confident he was
able to you know he would be able to
break through it if he just knew if he
you know put enough force the first time
he attacked he didn't know he'd go had a
blue vein and that's the thing Ichigo
doesn't know about it he doesn't know
anything about really Quincy abilities
let alone blue vein he would not be able
to activate this on command I mean it
wouldn't be like in a fight when you
know freakin Ross and sure Ken's headed
toward Ichigo he would just be able to
be like oh look they activate and then
you know he'll be able to like you know
resist it and like throw it away alright
he's not able to activate it on a whim
and also due to the fact that he's on
not used to using it he would not have a
very high limit with it yeah I was able
to stop a sword okay well I let's just
say he was able to let's just say it
could stop a normal Rasengan but still
I'm pretty sure Ichigo who's not used to
using this kind of technique and clearly
has its limits would be able to stop
something like a Ross and shuriken or
like a planetary Rasengan just using
blue vein which would be something that
we maybe have to use reflexively at that
point it might be able to lessen the
damage of it but it would certainly not
be able to stop it altogether and also
Naruto would be able to use this in
multiple succession because we've seen
he's been able to do that alright so
defensive techniques in terms of Naruto
he's able to use sage mode which
increases basically all his base stats
right away he's been able to take damage
like that he's able to lift up a giant
freaking stone frog so I would imagine
that his defensive capabilities have
increased somewhat he fell off for
exampie fell off that giant cliff and he
landed on the ground he flew like what
was that like ten stories in the
freaking air he fell and hit the ground
and he wasn't even barely rattled so
defensive clear abilities clearly
increased at that point also he's kind
of a master of Sage Mode he was able to
master it even beyond Jiraiya so it
would be fair to call him a sage mode
master also we have the ninetails cloak
and those are really the only two
defensive skills that Naruto has but the
ninetails cloak what I'm talking about
here is I'm not referring to the three
four tails you know blood red Naruto
crazy Berserker mode okay those are not
going to be included because you can't
have both you can't have the crazy
Berserker mode and the controlled form
trauma and naruto are on good terms
right now so let's just say that those
techniques that Nora was able to do like
the six tails and everything let's just
say those are not in the equation
anymore
the nine tails cloak he's got the kind
of the full control form and he also has
that version to form and he also has the
ability to turn into the Fox itself now
the only reason I didn't mention the
whole transformation thing is I consider
that more of an augmentation and then a
full-on attack ability because we will
see more than that but once he activates
the ninetails Fox you know we'll get
down to augmentation so the sage voted
nine tails cloak unlike ichigo's blue
vein he's mastered both of those he
can't go into both of them at the same
time I want to be clear on that he can't
go sage mode and full nine tails chakra
but if he does go into nine tails cloak
and nine Ichigo we're hitting it with
the gessica tensho not saying we'd be
able to stop the attack altogether but
he would take significant less damage
than if you were just in normal form you
have to give me that much fandom you
have to give me that much okay and aside
from that fact we also have to look at
the fact that Naruto has augmented
healing through the nine tails chakra
which is basically a second reserve of
chakra that's essentially infinite it
not it isn't infinite but it's
essentially a like we've never really
seen the nine tails uh you know really
run out of chakra until recent chapter
is when he's been portioning it out
through everybody and that would clearly
not be the case with this but he has
healing ability so you go to speed up
healing so Ichigo doesn't have that same
healing ability so right there you know
Naruto full ninetails chakra control
form cloak ichigo hits him with gets ago
even in bankai you know Naruto would be
injured a little bit but through his
healing abilities and through he can
just you know send out a couple shadow
clones as diversionary tactics while he
heals up I don't see much of a problem
here
so let's just ignore blue vein for the
moment let's just cut that out of the
equation through using ichigo's hollow
mask abilities and spiritual pressure
cushioning along with naruto's
nine-tails cushion that would be about
equal the only thing that's tipping the
scale here is Naruto's healing ability
that's the only thing that's tipping the
scale if it was just between nine tails
cloak versus Halla mask plus ichigo's
reishi cushion defense I could say
that's an even that's an even
justification there but Naruto can heal
Ichigo you can't
and now support characters are not
allowed next up is speed now which of
these characters has the great Ichigo
alright so yeah that one pretty much
right away I don't even have to really
give because there's not really a lot of
stuff to go off of here in terms of
speed Ichigo has his bankai ability
along with he has whole mass which
increases his speed further Naruto we've
seen he could you know run faster we
hasn't really mastered the bloody flip
the body flicker the teleportation
techniques so that doesn't really count
there you could say so I didn't write
down sage mode but you could say sage
mode he could run faster but I didn't
even include that because it would be so
miniscule in terms of just super powers
and the thing that I really wrote down
the only thing I wrote down in terms of
Naruto for speed would be the imperfect
yellow flash technique because we saw
after he activated the full nine tails
cloak he was able to like jump across a
freaking room and Killer Bee made that
comment oh I saw was a yellow flash yo
and that gave it credence to believe
that Naruto would basically you know
Matt like have the same ability as his
dad who'd be able to use the yellow
flash technique the same problem with
that is the same problem I had with blue
Fane it's imperfect even in the same
chapter I think Yamamoto even said
that's not you have to be careful how
you do how you use your new powers so
we've seen probably since then in or
just been able to master it a little bit
but we haven't seen him use it a very uh
we haven't seen him use it a lot and
there's probably a reason for that
because Naruto is not gifted at using
the nine tails you know speed now would
the yellow flash technique along with
bankai whole amounts would that be equal
sure if Naruto had it mastered if Naruto
had it mastered the point that Minato
had it then I would say speed would be
about the same but it's not so that's
why I gave speed to Ichigo next up is
augmentation abilities abilities that
they use to increase their own power I
might have mentioned a little bit of
these before because they go hand in
hand for example with Ichigo
we have bankai and we have hollow masks
those are two abilities that he has that
are augments but they also have a that
he also pretty much jumps to bankai
right away and whole masks if things get
really dicey other abilities you might
think why I'm not mentioning are
ichigo's fullbring which of course was
fused with his shikai which is why his
shikai is much considerably more
stronger than at what it used to be and
a hollow mass which of course we met
like he hasn't used it yet but let's
just say it was on the same level when
he fought against Aizen with the the two
stripes ring down the side which would
increase his spiritual pressure and
everything drastically there I didn't
put final get the content show for
reasons I previously mentioned so those
are in terms of his arguments so in
terms of Naruto four augments I mean
sage mode is one but I already kind of
you know flush that out anyway and oh by
the way sage mode is crap no sage mode
is not crap just taking away all the
offensive abilities that sage mode gives
Naruto the sensing ability and the
ability to you know select natural
natural energy and everything which by
the way in this neutral universe Naruto
would have at the same time it's sensing
abilities and be able to focus on
everything that would be a greater asset
than just sheer power but whenever I
pretty much flushed out sage mode the
augment is the nine tails chakra forms
he has the to cloak forms he can go into
and he's the ability to turn into the
actual Fox right now the major augment
behind this though is not just the fact
he's able to turn into the Fox it's
communication with Kurama and that's
probably one of the greatest augments
that he has is Naruto he's not alone
when he's fighting he has Kurama there
now to help him out sure but if we're
talking if we're talking before he
matched the nine tails this would be a
completely different fight I wouldn't
have included half the Rasengan
abilities because he wouldn't have had
them without the nine tails I wouldn't
have included the freakin nine tails
forms because he would go back to just
being a berserker but the fact of the
matter is now that he's gotten on good
terms with Kurama they're able to
communicate back and forth they have
this telepathy they're able to think of
better battle strategies Kurama is able
to basically tell him and you know when
he's being stupid or like no don't do
that it will get killed and he's also
able to gather chakra while Naruto is
off doing something else so yeah it's
better communication sure Ichigo has
zangetsu with him but song ketsu a
relationship with Ichigo is not the same
as with Kurama with Naruto
when ichigo's fighting and he's getting
his ass kicked you know we don't see
zangetsu pop in and be like hey ichigo
yeah you're about to die so here take
some of my reiatsu because his reactive
is kind of the same as ichigo so we
don't we don't ever see that happening
with zangetsu
there's hollow Ichigo with stepped in a
few times but he's only there just show
up if ichigo's about to get killed
that's the only way that Halloween
should go ever shows up and we're going
off
you know old hollow Ichigo back when you
is really cool um you know he's not
there to give him advice in any way
shape or form he only shows up if
ichigo's about to die he either takes
control of ichigo's body very briefly
and then goes away or he becomes full
hollow Ichigo for a little bit before he
goes away or he gets damaged to a degree
where he has to revert back so that's
the only way that he would show back up
so let's just say off the off the cuff
here you know Naruto kicks the shit out
of each ego and Ichigo you know on the
brink of death whole Ichigo takes over
he goes into full uber Jedi mode that he
used against Duke Yura in this form he
can use gessica tensho eyes away can he
still used yeah I probably can use guess
he didn't show he has cero now and he's
basically a berserker versus uh you know
tail beasts version Naruto I would still
say in that situation Naruto would still
win he would probably have to go full
tailed form beast mode
he would stuff to go full tail beast
mode probably take this thing on but
we've seen that even this form has
limits you know when Ichigo when you cut
off his horn and you know freakin cero
blows up in his face he had to resort
back to his regular form so even though
he's a beserker and he has an insane
amount of react to an insane amount of
power SuperSpeed and everything with
sonido
there's still a limit he could still get
broken you know tail beasts freakin
Bijou dominoes freakin shoot Ichigo and
that has to be worth at least a cero
you have to say at least the tailed
beast Buju dama which look what this
shit can do
yeah I think that would maybe at least
equal the amount of cero ability a
little bit so just in terms of that in
terms of the help that Kurama would give
Naruto in terms of you know augmented
powers I got to go with Naruto on this
one I know you guys are going to hate me
because out of the five groups I came up
with I essentially gave Naruto three out
of the four so far so a flash group last
group we have miscellaneous abilities
abilities that I didn't really other
things I didn't only get to mention in
other parts of the video for Ichigo I
just have the ability of flights which
somebody mentioned the ability to fly or
if you don't want to say flight ability
to maintain you know he can maintain his
stance in the air we've seen Ichigo can
stay in the air indefinitely let's just
refer to lay this flight for now other
things the Naruto has are basically just
ninja tactics which I kind of already
mentioned ninja tactics he's able to you
know he's better at deception he's
better at that stuff kind of stuff and
Ichigo is and that's not fighting dirty
that's just fighting how a ninja fights
that's like two completely different you
know ways how you fight so once again
compensation some people said that
because Naruto I mean Ichigo was able to
fly an r2 can't there for Ichigo would
have the main advantage okay well let's
look at it like this and I made this
comparison on my livestream but let's
just look at it like this okay so let's
have like a tank versus a plane and you
immediately saying oh the plane wins
because the plane can fly it's faster
has better maneuverability than just a
slow sluggish tank which is grounded
that's not really that true I mean sure
the plane could you know move a lot
faster but at the same time one hit from
the tank it might be hard but if it
happens and I'm certainly happened
before and you know conflicts and
everything it can go down kind of the
same thing with Ichigo Ichigo combined
with speed and his flight can maintain
an altitude you know for an indefinite
period of time
Noora on the other hand sage mode nine
tails chakra he can propel himself into
the air but he cannot maintain an
altitude he can't we've seen him in his
fight against Mew for example the other
second su Chi cago Mew had the
levitation jutsu he could stay in the
air for indefinite period of time or
until he ran out of chalk
so how Naruto Calif on him was launched
himself in the everything ninetails
chakra he used a planetary Rasengan to
attack MU along with his chakra arms
which were able to extend his reach
indefinitely and that's how he took down
mu so in this situation I'm going to say
you might be saying like Oh ichigo's you
know he has flight and he's super fast
with his bankai and you said he
Ichigo would win in terms of speed so
there's no way Ichigo like Naruto would
be able to hit him when he's up in the
air you know like like I'm he's was it
around like that there's no way Ichigo
Naruto would be able to hit him with
rust and shuriken or anything um once
again I got to say sage mode which
better senses things nine tails chakra
which basically it has a mind of its own
essentially I mean look perfect example
look at Sasuke after Sasuke mastered the
Sharingan essentially he was able to
dodge Naruto's moves no problem with his
speed and just because he was able to
see Naruto's movements but because the
nine tails chakra had a mind of its own
you pretty much have two things coming
at you at the same time and going back
to shadow clones conceivably more than
two so take whatever number of shadow
clones Naruto has and double that
because the nine tails chakra and you
got attacks coming from every direction
the speed is only really good if you're
facing a one opponent or a lower number
of opponents that can't hit you but you
know let's say you have a plane in the
air one plane one tank the tanks
probably have a hard time hitting the
plane you have a freaking hundred tanks
on the ground all launching up at the
same time that might cause an issue if
you don't believe me there then you know
Naruto would go full freakin nine tails
chakra form into freakin the Fox you
know ten story Fox there versus Ichigo I
think your flight abilities kind of been
you know nullify your flight advantage
been nullified there but at the same
time that's going off with a lot of ifs
there so just for the sake of you know
ifs and everything I'm going to go with
in terms of other or miscellaneous
abilities I'm going to say they're both
equal
so final round up in terms of attack
give that to Norco and in terms of speed
Ichigo in terms of augments Naruto and
in terms of flight or other I was going
to say Naruto on this but just to be you
know just to be even I'll give even
there so with with this ability we'd do
with this uh you know group and
everything I've set up I have to say
I've said it before I'll say it again
I'm gonna get scrutiny for saying it
Naruto would win in a fight between them
so that's my first episode of checking
showdowns by the way i don't know if i'm
i keep calling it that hope you guys
enjoy it I'll I'm dreading the comments
on this this is probably going to be
this is going to be freaking - this
gonna be a POC - left apocalyptic but at
the same time this is just me I told you
this is the way I choose to set off the
fight if this is not what you agree with
fine more power to you and you'll
probably make your opinion very well
known in the comments below
go watch somebody else who you do agree
with there's many people on YouTube that
do this kind of crossover fighting thing
and this is how I chose to do mine so
you know there you go and just they just
before before I sign off here let me
just say one thing and I know yeah I I
just feel I have to mention this okay
this is all for fun okay this this is
all for fun guys you know at the end of
the day they're fictional characters
coming up with you know concepts and
everything I had a lot of fun doing this
that'sthat's the reason I made the video
was because I'm like oh man if I can
think of you know like how would it get
to content show do against you know
Naruto but Norton has this but Ichigo
has that you know that that was fun for
me to make these videos it really was
but there are people out there I'm not
saying all of you but there are people
out there that take this to the next
level
I've seen many flame wars erupt in the
comment sections in videos talking about
this and then the forms and everything
and people cursing each other and like
you so bitch you know Naruto would lose
a ghost Ichigo right away you know this
is thick there's no need there's no call
or need for that okay there's no need
for you guys to write you know paragraph
after paragraph after paragraph oh this
some could be considered a short story
about just you berating somebody else
because they think somebody else would
win in a fight alright it's just it just
it really just makes so even if someone
were to to leave a comment on this and
you know you're wrong about everything
North ichigo would win no questions
asked i'm not gonna get butthurt over
that i'm not gonna get if someone leaves
a massive conman you know they call the
freaking curse words and beacon of free
control i'm not gonna get you know hurt
over that i'm not gonna sit here and cry
in my bed why did they say she go is
loose ain't she going down loose it's
the best he's awesome
he could use get to get that show he's
alright I love you Ichigo I love you
you're amazing you're amazing so I focus
the fuck out here I don't care about you
but Ichigo you're amazing in every way
shape or form so yeah just like this is
what you're trying to understand this is
not like my firm dogma and belief this
is not something I'm gonna like take to
my grave where it's like all my
tombstone it's gonna read you Naruto
Beauty go for the win you know it's not
going to be it's not going to be
something like that that's my firm
belief this is just me having fun
looking at their abilities comparing and
contrasting them figuring out who would
win in my own opinion with my own
criteria that's it nothing more and
that's all it should be when you comment
on this video so with that I say ty via
fans and haters and trolls alike teching
101 signing out